wukar.com 2015-05-15

# Privacy Policy & Cookies - WUKAR Videos

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.wukar.com and WUKAR, INC. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to WUKAR, INC. include www.wukar.com and WUKAR. The WUKAR website is a News and Information site. By using the WUKAR website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

 **Collection of your Personal Information**

WUKAR may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase WUKAR’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. WUKAR may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender and race. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by WUKAR. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the WUKAR website.

WUKAR encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from WUKAR so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. WUKAR is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the WUKAR website.

 **Use of your Personal Information**

WUKAR collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

WUKAR may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from WUKAR and its affiliates. WUKAR may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

WUKAR does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

WUKAR may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. WUKAR may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to WUKAR, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

WUKAR will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on WUKAR or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of WUKAR; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of WUKAR, or the public.

 **Use of Cookies**

The WUKAR website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize WUKAR pages, or register with WUKAR site or services, a cookie helps WUKAR to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same WUKAR website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the WUKAR features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the WUKAR services or websites you visit.

 **Security of your Personal Information**

To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, WUKAR uses the Cloudflare technology.

 **  Children Under Thirteen**

WUKAR does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

Disconnecting your WUKAR Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your WUKAR account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR WUKAR ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their “My Account” page. Users may also contact us via email or telephone..

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from WUKAR by contacting us here:

\- Web page: www.wukar.com

\- Email: support@teamwukar.com

\- Phone: 877-768-4660

Changes to this Statement

WUKAR will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. WUKAR encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how WUKAR is protecting your information.

Contact Information

WUKAR welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that WUKAR has not adhered to this Statement, please contact WUKAR at:

WUKAR, INC.  
8605 Santa Monica Blvd.  
Suite 13160  
West Hollywood, CA 90069
